[
  {
    "question": "Fought in the War of 1812",
    "answers": ["US", "GB"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": ["US", "GB"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in World War I",
    "answers": ["US", "GB", "FR", "DE", "RU", "IT", "AU", "CA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in World War II",
    "answers": ["US", "GB", "FR", "DE", "RU", "JP", "IT", "AU", "CA", "CN"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Waterloo",
    "answers": ["GB", "FR", "NL", "DE"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Gettysburg",
    "answers": ["US"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Stalingrad",
    "answers": ["RU", "DE"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Vietnam War",
    "answers": ["US", "VN"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Korean War",
    "answers": ["KR", "CN", "US"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Gulf War",
    "answers": ["US", "UK", "SA", "IQ"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the French Revolution",
    "answers": ["FR", "GB", "DE", "RU", "AT"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Hastings",
    "answers": ["GB", "FR"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": ["FR", "GB", "DE", "RU", "AT", "ES", "IT", "PL"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the American Civil War",
    "answers": ["US"]
  }
]
